[{"answer": "I was.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Were you a good hog slayer?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, I tell a lot of stories in my standup act that, you know, or my points of view of different things.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you do standup, the kind of standup I like, you've got to tell the truth and you know hopefully you've had some interesting things.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "To put it mildly, haven't you?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, I can't think of anything.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Is there anything about your life that you can't joke about?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "My battle with food and my weight is the core of every -- of my alcoholism, of everything.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Your weight, the way you look, everything?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I need to lose some weight.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "And how are you feeling these days about the way you look?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I remember working at Hormel very well.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Did you remember that experience well?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I was.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Were you a good hog slayer?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Were they eating a bacon sandwich at the time, don't they?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I mean, they are animals.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Do you feel guilty?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "You know, when I don't feel -- you know, I got fired from Hormel.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Do you ever wonder if your life hadn't taken a deviation in standup, do you ever wonder if you could -- if you were still there now?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "So -- yes, it was first --", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, me, Mike, and Mo, who are still buddies of mine to this day, there's nothing to do in Ottumwa, Iowa, after 10:00.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "You did what?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Terrifying.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "What was that moment like?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "The first time I got offered a paying job, $15, I was in University of Iowa and I had some standup.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "When was the moment that you realized this could be a career, and not just a bit of fun for you?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "You know, but people have to understand, I haven't talked to her, you know, face to face in almost 18 years.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "I mean, is that a good thing or not a good thing for you?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Do you ever?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Do you follow her on Twitter?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, it was great fun because we met in 1983.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "But I would imagine for a while, it must have been electrifying, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sure the alcoholic part of me, the self-destructive part of me misses it.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Did any part of you missing that kind of chaotic exciting, you're center stage?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Like I say, there's that voice inside of me, it's not a happy voice that does.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "When you go to a newsstand, do you ever have a little thought (ph) of, oh, I wish they were putting me on the cover again?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "I'd say good luck with your show.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "And what would you say to her if she's watching?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Part of her, no.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Do you think she'll be pleased that you're happy?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Rather impressive remarks there I think, Tom, to your old friend Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, you have to understand he grew up in a -- much like me in a small town in -- in Austria in his case.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "What do you make of what's been going on?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Were you -- were you as shocked as everybody else?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, we see each other.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "About what's been going on?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, the only joke that I can crack is that he can no longer make fun of the women that I've been with.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "At what point can you crack a joke about this?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "He's always been tough about that stuff.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "But to him personally, just as a guy, a friend of yours, how is he dealing with it?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I think it's a go.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Is that a go, or is it -- but might that happen?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Absolutely, we've been talking about it.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "You've been talking about it?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I think Arnold is a great man.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "The -- what kind of man is Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "You think he has physical aspirations or is that pretty well dead in the water, do you think?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Do you feel because of that, because politics has now been shut down really for him, that the movies, which is what propelled him really into the stratosphere, that that may be the love again for him, that he may just go back to that?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "It is torturous, and it's monotonous.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "I mean, it's like a -- it's a torturous process, isn't it?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "You've made 100 movies?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I loved \"True Lies\" --", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Which is your favorite?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I think there was one.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "The one you don't like to talk about in civilized company?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I was about a half ounce a day --", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "-- at your worst, what are we talking in terms of consumption?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "-- of cocaine.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, I will tell you this.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Did you remember how that made you feel?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you -- do you drink at all now?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Literally nothing at all?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I watch people sometimes, normal people.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "And do you ever get tempted?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "RNOLD: I have regrets about the way I acted, you know, when I was using drugs and alcohol.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Did you have any regrets about it, or is it something that happened to you, that you're just pleased you moved on that was for a long time probably quite a bit fun?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, relationships-wise, if your mom leaves when you're four, you know, anything is possible.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "How much of what went on then do you think determined how you became in your earlier adulthood?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Well, after I got sober, you know, you -- you spin through things, and you work on things.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "What happened to the abuser?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I just -- I just said what I had to say.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "What did you do?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Did you hit him?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "And did it bring you any kind of closure?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "The best advice was to make it the priority of my day every day above my relationship witness, above my career.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Who gave it to you?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Well, I got a lot of advice.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "And who gave you that advice?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I love Charlie.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "When you see someone like Charlie going through what he's been through the last few months, what's been your -- your view watching from afar?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "That's the immorality of -- of everywhere.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "I mean, there in a nutshell is the immorality of Hollywood, isn't it?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "I -- there was a night.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "What in the end made you stop?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "You know, he's lost a lot this year.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "Does he have anyone around him that can give him that hug?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "I think Ashton would be great.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "What did you think of that decision?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "Well, if I'd have continued partying, obviously, I wouldn't have anything.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Have you managed to, despite all the partying and the extravagances and so on, have you retained enough to be pretty comfortable the rest of your life?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "Security has brought me happiness.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 886, "question": "Money?", "qSentId": 885}, {"answer": "Yes, we'd like to do that.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 930, "question": "Is that something that you'd like to do now?", "qSentId": 929}, {"answer": "I hope so, yes.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 935, "question": "Do you think you'd be a good father?", "qSentId": 934}, {"answer": "You know, I liked -- sounds crazy but I liked Bob Hope a lot when I first moved out here because my dad used to laugh at him, get home from work late and I could hear him and my dad howling laughing and so, when I got to a Bob Hope special, that was a big thing.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 947, "question": "Who makes you laugh out loud?", "qSentId": 946}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 952, "question": "Is he the guy that all stand-ups revere?", "qSentId": 951}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 955, "question": "He is, you know?", "qSentId": 954}, {"answer": "Because he dealt with the harshest stuff, with drug addiction, with -- you know, horrible injuries that happened to him.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 957, "question": "Why was he so special?", "qSentId": 956}, {"answer": "I'm Just finishing a movie that -- Dax Sheppard, who is the funniest man in America now is directing, with Bradley Cooper, as I said, playing a bad guy, and working -- movie stuff, I'm on the road.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 961, "question": "What are you working on?", "qSentId": 960}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 969, "question": "And you're also involved in independent films, right?", "qSentId": 968}, {"answer": "I would probably be more careful with my career in the '90s, you know, instead of taking a lot of things --", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 975, "question": "Given your often outrageous life, if I could give you five minutes to relive one moment in your life and it couldn't be wives or children, what would it be?", "qSentId": 974}, {"answer": "I would say -- I don't mean to sound cliche but my marriage to Ashley, because I quit the marriage thing.", "docId": "110724pmt", "aSentId": 985, "question": "The single greatest thing, do you think?", "qSentId": 984}]